Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
My, how imperfect. Since he's able to wield that sword, I had assumed he must be a member of that bloodline.
Why don't we show them what you really are?
How do you feel?
溶ける夢 高る割の群れが 正しく生きる本能ならば なぜあたしはここにいるの 期待通りなど ごめんなの自分で やれるからさ
どうだっていい理屈ばっか 張り付いた 張り持っての世界を生きてく
誰かのためじゃない 今はまだ 自分に追いつくまで
がむしゃらでじめき飛ばした 身体中の声が 翼広げて
どんな未来も舞うよ 風吹いて 自分を追い越すまで
?
oğlum Mmmm?
どんな所に?
どんな況です?
失敬してください…
そこに誰かは死んlicher 西親里星は…
Come on. No.
Hey you. Good to see ya.
What the heck are you?
I can't believe you'd say that to me. I've been your closest companion for a while now.
I'm pretty sure I'd remember a guy like you.
Ah well. Doesn't make any difference. I got a chance to manifest in the physical world so I'm taking it.
Your body belongs to me.
Tell me what's going on right now!
You should be glad it's a pretty sweet deal for you. I mean really. You wanna win this? Then all you have to do is leave it to me.
You shut up! I'll beat this guy with nothing but my own power!
Quit adding the limit to control of your mind already. Just relax and let go of your consciousness.
A half fight like you doesn't set a chance in this fight.
That's not up to you now, is it?
You know what? It's kinda perfect that you're looming over my head like that!
Cause if you're up there then I can use you to climb straight to the sky!
Some places can't be climbed to!
You should just give up.
This world is no use for someone like you. A poor, magicless fool. You might as well give it all up right now!
You are born a loser you worthless runt!
Run! Run!
Run!
Give up!
There was a time in my life when I might have given up! But that's all behind me now!
Put that soul behind me now!
my magic is never giving up!
My magic is never giving up!
The chick is never giving up!
What? How's he back on his feet?
The leaves of a clover are said to each contain one thing.
In the first three dwell integrity, hope, and love.
The fourth leaf is given over to good luck.
And in the fifth, there lives the devil.
This feeling, it's not magic.
What's with him?
Something isn't right here.
So do you have this big dramatic transformation?
Did you expect me to be impressed by God or something?
You're mine!
I can see that you're a little quicker on your feet now!
But how long will this new trick of yours hold out?
Do you think I was gonna fall for that twice?
Damn! He's not messing around! How did he get so strong?
How did he get so strong?
This next attack can't possibly miss!
Huh?
Uh!
Eh!
Do you think I was gonna fall for that twice?!
You think I was gonna fall for that twice?
Huh?
Uh!
Um…
It's not messing around!
How did he get so strong…
He's not messing around!
This next attack, can't possibly miss!
Huh?
What's happening?
My body's chilled to the bone, like I'm floating in a freezing lake.
And my mind feels clearer than ever.
And my physical strength is overflowing!
I thought for certain he'd lose consciousness, but he's still maintaining control.
Not only does the Demon Slayer Sword conduct anti-magic energy in massive amounts,
it absorbs the magic of all who touch it.
Therefore, no one should be able to wield this blade.
But you are without magic, and so its power courses through you.
You've been dictating its ebb and flow from the beginning without even realizing it.
When I used my blood to heal you, it increased the rate of that power's movement.
In doing so, I intentionally removed any limitations on the sword's capabilities.
Now your magic power will burst forth in a massive wave,
and you will become the vessel for this torrent of anti-magic.
So this is not going to take my phone through its power!
Yes!
So this will be one moment.
I want to make the arms capable of throwing things in the ground!
Should I Gigrap your house?
I wonder, though.
Good luck!
Oh, my God.
What is this awful feeling?
Due to your body's mutation, the mana did not dwell within you. Simply put, you're defective. But because of that, you're able to hold the sword.
How the hell is this happening?
You aren't anything special. Not in the slightest. And that is precisely what makes you extraordinary.
I want you out of my side!
Now that you're in this form, all magic is powerless against you.
Finish him.
The sky...
No! No, no, no, no! No! No!
It's not fair! I stepped on so many people to get where I am now! I can't lose to you!
You always kick your friends down! But my friends helps me be better! Stronger! Like me, right?
No!
Asta, he's so strong, and the way he was fighting, he was like a different person.
He looks so terrifying now.
Like a...
Just kill me. Go ahead, I'm ready.
You must be crazy!
Huh?
It's better if I keep you alive so you can help other people that you hurt!
And then I'm gonna make you apologize to all of them!
Now pat yourself up and get going!
You may be all bloody and gross looking, but that doesn't mean that I have to go easy on you!
What the heck is your problem?!
Damn! I can't catch a break! You're a tough guy!
This is out of character!
Baby! Now that the magic stone's been destroyed, my head's starting to feel a little bit lighter!
Oh man...
You sure you're okay? Cause you fell to the ground so hard and-
Someone like you is headed straight to the top, that's for sure. Makes me wonder...
If we'd met sooner, maybe you and I could've made each other better too...
Thank you, Asta.
Dude, are you sleeping?! Keep your eyes open so I know you're alive!
I'm overthinking it. He's still Asta.
I'm normal now. That was weird.
What was all that black stuff earlier? It felt like I was fighting something inside of a dream.
I had some kind of mysterious power, so that was pretty awesome.
I mean, I owned it! Is this what everyone else feels like when they use their magic abilities?
Oh god, my whole body started hurting all of a sudden!
And it feels like my insides are bleeding like crazy too!
I'm gonna die! Hey, can somebody please help me?!
Help you?
Look at us.
Wait, the rest of you are in bad shape too?!
Hey, you two! You got recovery magic?
Come on, don't tell me you already bit the dust!
Oh good, you're alive!
Don't just lay there!
Oh dear, I hope I'm not too heavy.
No. In fact, the pressure feels kind of comforting.
He's way different now!
Mar, stop it.
Hello!
Well, it's gonna take a whole bunch of trips back and forth,
but I guess the only thing for me to do is to carry everybody back to safety!
That's not necessary.
It's you.
The Queen's here.
That took care of the Eye of the Midnight Sun and all those Diamond Army soldiers,
so that ought to make us even for you fixing my arms, right?
And you did it without me having to involve myself in the least. Imperfect though you may be,
I must say, you've done quite well.
It's no big deal.
Hey, while I've got you here, and I kind of hate to ask this, but...
Do you think you could heal everyone real quick too?
Do you?
Oh, that's also unnecessary.
Do you think you could heal everyone real quick?
Huh? What did she...
Noelle!
Blood Creation Magic.
Fresh Blood Execution Ground.
They're going to be okay. I just know it.
You're right.
Her power is horrifying.
Show up out of nowhere, and then you do think...
Yes, my magic allows me to manipulate blood as I please.
Ever since I cast that healing spell on you, I've maintained total control over your blood as well.
I am the queen here.
Why should I fulfill the requests of a pathetic worm such as yourself?
The only one who must obey is you.
Blood Magic. Puppet's Blood.
Let him go!
That aside, your death would prove inconvenient for me.
You alone will receive healing.
Blood Recovery Magic. Curse-breaking blood-filled cocoon.
Stay by me, and you may wreak all the havoc you like.
Casting such advanced spells one right after the other...
This isn't like the spirit's power.
Just being close to it is giving me chills.
She's worse than I thought.
As for that sword, if I cannot wield it myself, I simply need to be the master of the one who can.
And you've just demonstrated how you use it.
So for as long as you live, you're going to carry this weapon as though it were mine.
No! What's happening?
All this time, she was only after the Anti-Magic Sword?
And now for your first order.
I want you to kill every one of these weaklings with your own hands.
Do a perfect job and leave no one alive.
Asta!
No!
MARTINO!
Sunbeinsui!
voir!
Asta!
You have a mess.
You want any animal out of me?
If you are ill, you can see another gold cell replacement.
You cannot hang with them in line while you start reading,
oh please, there will be a cool number.
You will be the best support.
The sky is the sky.
The sky is so fluid in the air.
手を回したら、届きそうだけど
行ったり来たり、消えたりばったり
謎の場その場しのぎみたいなシーンが
たくさん
これはボリューツのデカくさん
どうぞ百貫
ここでバッター
すべて合算したら発散すれば
愛だろう恋だろう
名もは僕らが通り越して
まだ名前などないその輝きも
I'm so happy to see you in the middle of the night.
It's a dream.
Here we go.
This is a dream.
This is not a dream.
I don't want to change.
So the queen just wanted control of Asta's anti-magic all along.
Damn, with powers like that, no wonder she isn't aging.
Black Clover, page 64.
The Red Thread of Fate.
Vanessa?
What kind of spell is that?
Yeah that's right.
I see her left.
It was good.
في jarben에 crossed Latina.
I'm going.
Let's find her in a new place.
I went.
Thread of Fateollo.
And another lover.
And another lover,
and then I took the Reinhold пер defiance.